permuto.com 2013-06-05

# Buysight: Privacy Policy

## ****[](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.permuto.com&sealid=101 "TRUSTe Permuto Verification")****

## **Buysight, Inc. Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**

This privacy policy is intended to inform you of the collection, use and disclosure of information that we collect.  All references to “we,” “us” and “our” are intended to mean Buysight, Inc. (“Buysight”), and all references to “you” and “your” are intended to mean users who have been exposed to our services.  “Partner Sites” refer to advertiser and publisher websites that use our services.  Because our Privacy Policy may be updated periodically, we encourage you to review these pages on a regular basis.

Buysight is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the Web site www.Buysight.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at [privacy@buysight.com](mailto:privacy@buysight.com) .  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

 **Our Services**

At Buysight, we collect certain anonymous and non-personally identifiable information about users in order to display effective advertisements.  Based on the behavior and preferences of the users that we have identified, we seek to group those users into certain categories.  We then seek to display the most relevant advertisements to the users in those categories.  

 **The Anonymous Data**

Anonymous Data  
The Anonymous Data that we collect about users through our services is anonymous, non-personally identifiable information and may include such information as your Internet Protocol address, your browser, and your activity on the websites of our partners (the “Anonymous Data”).  (An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is an address on the internet that is automatically assigned to your computer when you establish a connection on the Internet.)

Personally Identifiable Information  
We do collect certain personally identifiable information if you register with us on our website.  This personally identifiable information, which may include your name, company information, address, and your website information (collectively, “PII”), is only captured when you register on our site. This PII is not shared, sold or rented to any other third parties.  If you would like to have this PII changed, you can contact us at the email below.

How We Collect the Anonymous Data  
We may collect this Anonymous Data, directly or indirectly, from our network of Partner Sites, or we may purchase this Anonymous Data from other third party providers.  

For Anonymous Data that we purchase from third party providers, the Privacy Policy for such third party providers applies to the provisioning of that Anonymous Data.  The use of that Anonymous Data by Buysight, however, is governed by this Policy.    

For Anonymous Data that we collect, directly or indirectly, we typically employ the use of “pixel tags” and/or “cookies.”  Pixel tags are small bits of code that provide a method of delivery information on a webpage which allow the operator of the page or a third party to collect information about the users of the page.  Cookies are small text files that are stored on the browser of your computer that uniquely identify your browser and provide information to the cookie sender.  Many websites send cookies to the browsers that are visiting those sites, and many browsers are initially configured to accept cookies.  You may be able to change your browser settings to refuse cookies or to alert you of when a cookie has been placed on your browser.  Check your browser for details.  

Use of Anonymous Data  
We use the Anonymous Data that we collect in order to display advertisements that we believe may be relevant to you.  In seeking to identify relevant advertisements, we use this Anonymous Data to create and refine user segments, develop and refine algorithms, and to understand better how your interaction with a website might be of interest to advertisers.  We do not link any Anonymous Data to the PII collected on our website.  

Further, we may share aggregated information that we have learned from the use of the Anonymous Data with third parties.  Such information may include traffic patterns, sales, and other site information.  For example, we might share statistics on how many customers viewed or clicked on a particular advertisement.

We do not sell the Anonymous Data to third parties.   

 **Blogs and Testimonials**

Please note that if you use a blog on our site, you should be aware that anything you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  As a result, we are not responsible for the PII you choose to submit in these forums.  Some of our clients have chosen to post testimonials on our site.  We have obtained the approvals of such clients to post their PII along with the testimonial.  

Please note that we have a third party cookie, Google Sitemap, on our site which assists us with the operation, maintenance and analytics of the website.  

 **Anonymous Data Security**

We employ reasonable industry standard measures to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or destruction of the Anonymous Data.  While we are committed to ensuring the security of the Anonymous Data, you should be aware that no Anonymous Data protection measures can provide 100% guarantee of security.  Consequently, we do not warrant or guarantee the security of the Anonymous Data.  

 **Anonymous Data Retention**

Buysight does not use or retain any PII for purposes of delivering advertising or any other services. Buysight may maintain Anonymous Data for up to 18 months unless required to do otherwise by law. Summarized data, consisting of aggregated statistical data not attributable to a uniquely identifiable entity, may be stored indefinitely.

**How to Opt-Out of Our Services**

There are two principal ways that you may opt out of our services:  

1) As mentioned before, you may opt out of our services by changing the cookie settings on your browser.  Again, please see your browser settings (under the Help menu) for more details.  

2) You may also opt-out by clicking [this link](http://preferences.buysight.com/) and following the instructions provided on that page.  You may also choose to opt out of our services through the Network Advertising Intiative page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and following the instructions therein.  Please note that after choosing to opt-out, if you use a different computer or a different browser, or if you delete or block browser cookies, you may need to repeat the opt-out steps.  
 ** **

**Changes to Buysight's Corporate Structure**

If all or part of Buysight is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, the Anonymous Data and PII gathered by Buysight may be transferred as part of that transaction. Buysight will take reasonable measures to ensure that such Anonymous Data is used in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy under which it was collected.  If such a change in Buysight’s corporate structure occurs, you will be notified as described below in the section entitled “Your Consent and Right to Change this Policy.”

 **Disclosure**

The above notwithstanding, we may disclose any of the Anonymous Data, any PII or any other information we collect when we believe that we have a legal obligation to do so.  For example, we may disclose any of the above in order to (i) protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served or (ii) protect or defend our proprietary rights.

 **Disclaimer**

We have no control over, nor any responsibility for, the privacy policies and/or content of any of our Partner Sites.  As a result, we disclaim any and all responsibility for, or affiliation with, any third party cookies, pixels or practices.   

 **Your Consent & Our Right to Change This Policy**

By visiting our website (Buysight.com) and/or the website of any of our partners, you hereby consent to our collection, storage, and dissemination of your Anonymous Data as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy materially, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of such changes. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

 **Effective Date**

This policy was updated on December 2, 2010.

 **How To Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact [privacy@buysight.com](mailto:privacy@buysight.com) .

U.S. Mail:

Buysight, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy  
945 Stewart Dr.  
Sunnyvale, CA 94085
